<resources>
    <string name="app_name">CountryCustomListView</string>
    <string name="bangladesh_short_details">
Bangladesh has a strong track . . .
    </string>
    <string name="bangladesh_long_details">
        Bangladesh has a strong track record of growth and development, even in times of elevated global uncertainty.  A robust demographic dividend, strong ready-made garment (RMG) exports, resilient remittance inflows, and stable macroeconomic conditions have supported rapid economic growth over the past two decades.

Bangladesh tells a remarkable story of poverty reduction and development. From being one of the poorest nations at birth in 1971, Bangladesh reached lower-middle income status in 2015. It is on track to graduate from the UN’s Least Developed Countries (LDC) list in 2026. Poverty declined from 11.8 percent in 2010 to 5.0 percent in 2022, based on the international poverty line of $2.15 a day (using 2017 Purchasing Power Parity exchange rate). Moreover, human development outcomes improved along many dimensions.
        Despite these gains, inequality has slightly narrowed in rural areas and widened in urban areas. The country did make a rapid recovery from the COVID-19 pandemic supported by prudent macroeconomic policies with estimated GDP growth of 6.0 percent in FY23. However, the economy faces considerable challenges with rising inflationary pressure, energy shortages, a balance-of-payments deficit, and a revenue shortfall. While the trade deficit narrowed in FY23, a contraction in financial account deficit resulted in a Balance of Payments (BoP) deficit and a decline in foreign exchange reserves.

Real GDP growth is expected to slow in FY24 as ongoing import suppression measures disrupt economic activity. Growth is expected to re-accelerate over the medium term, as inflationary pressure eases, external conditions improve, and reform implementation gains momentum. Over the medium term, the balance of payments is projected to return to a surplus as financial inflows recover and remittance inflows rise, supported by strong demand for workers in the Gulf region.

To achieve its vision of attaining upper middle-income status by 2031, Bangladesh needs to create jobs through a competitive business environment, increase human capital and build a skilled labor force, build efficient infrastructure, and establish a policy environment that attracts private investment.

Development priorities include diversifying exports beyond the RMG sector; resolving financial sector vulnerabilities; making urbanization more sustainable and strengthening public institutions, including fiscal reforms to generate more domestic revenue for development. Addressing infrastructure gaps would accelerate growth. Addressing vulnerability to climate change and natural disasters will help Bangladesh to continue to build resilience to future shocks. Pivoting towards green growth would support the sustainability of development outcomes for the next generation.
    </string>
    <string name="india_short_details">
India is a partner in advancing . . .
    </string>
    <string name="india_long_details">
        India is a partner in advancing USAID’s shared objectives to support clean energy, environment, climate challenges, health, open and inclusive digital ecosystems, inclusive economic growth, and the COVID-19 response in India and across South and Central Asia and the Indo-Pacific region.

India is a leading global power and a key U.S. partner in the Indo-Pacific and the world. The U.S. supports India’s rise as a leader and its development assistance to other countries, including Afghanistan, where we share economic and humanitarian interests. USAID also leverages India’s growing human and financial resources through partnerships, with both public and private actors, that catalyze innovation and entrepreneurship to solve critical local and global development challenges.
        India has the second-highest cases of global COVID-19 infections. USAID support has helped India strengthen health system resilience, readiness, response capacity, address stigma, and mobilize innovative financing mechanisms for emergency preparedness and response to the pandemic. USAID also helped India to address bottlenecks at different stages of the supply chain for HIV, TB, contraceptive, and other critical healthcare drugs and equipment, which are vital both for India and the world given that India’s pharmaceutical industry supplies 80 percent of the world’s medicines.

High rates of child and maternal death, widespread malnutrition, and persistently high TB and HIV rates threaten the lives and productivity of India’s expanding population. Exacerbating India’s health challenges, access to clean water and functioning toilets escapes about 40 percent of the population—making India home to the world’s highest number of diarrhea-related deaths in children under 5. USAID leverages Indian resources to strengthen the reach, affordability and quality of health care services. Also, with USAID support, since 2014, India has declared more than 4,000 cities open defecation-free, reducing the potential for health hazards.
    </string>
    <string name="pakistan_short_details">
        Pakistan emerged on the world . . .
    </string>
    <string name="pakistan_long_details">
        Pakistan emerged on the world map as an independent sovereign state in August 1947, as a result of the division of the British Indian Empire. With a land area of 881,913 sq. km. [including FATA (Federal Administered Tribal Areas) and FANA (Federal Administered Northern Areas)], its population stands at nearly 172.80 million, according to the 2008 Census. Historically, this is one of the most ancient lands known to man. Its cities flourished before Babylon was built; its people practiced the art of good living and citizenship before the celebrated ancient Greeks.

The region traces its history back to at least 2,500 years before Christ, when a highly developed civilization flourished in the Indus Valley. Excavations at Harappa, Mohenjodaro and Kot Diji have brought to light evidence of an advanced civilization flourishing here even in most ancient times. Around 1,500 B.C. the Aryans conquered this region and slowly pushed the Hindu inhabitants further east, towards the Ganges Valley. Later, the Persians occupied the northern regions in 5th century B.C. The Greeks came in 327 B.C., under Alexander of Macedonia, and ran through the region like a meteor. In 712 A.D. the Arabs, led by Mohammed Bin Qasim, landed somewhere near what is now Karachi, and ruled the lower half of Pakistan for two hundred years. During this time Islam took root and influenced the life, culture and traditions of the inhabitants of the region.

From 10th century A.D. onwards, a systematic conquest of Indo-Pakistan by the Muslims from Central Asia began and lasted up to 18th century A.D., when the British colonized the Sub-continent and ruled for nearly 200 years (for 100 years over what is now Pakistan). The Muslim revival began towards the end of the last century when Sir Syed Ahmed Khan, a renowned leader and educationist, launched a movement for intellectual renaissance of the Indian Muslims. In 1930, the well-known poet/philosopher, Dr. Mohammed Iqbal conceived the idea of a separate state for the Muslims of the Sub-continent, and in 1940, the All-India Muslim League adopted the famous Pakistan Resolution.

After seven years of untiring struggle, under the brilliant leadership of Quaid-e-Azam Mohammed Ali Jinnah, Pakistan emerged on the world map as a sovereign state on August 14, 1947, when the British Indian Empire was partitioned into two independent states – India and Pakistan.
    </string>
    <string name="nepal_short_details">
        Nepal officially the Federal . . .
    </string>
    <string name="nepal_long_details">
        Nepal officially the Federal Democratic Republic of Nepal is a landlocked central Himalayan country in South Asia. Nepal is divided into 7 states and 77 districts and 753 local units including 6 metropolises, 11 sub-metropolises, 246 municipal councils and 481 villages. It has a population of 26.4 million and is the 93rd largest country by area. Bordering China in the north and India in the south, east, and west, it is the largest sovereign Himalayan state.  Nepal has a diverse geography, including fertile plains, subalpine forested hills, and eight of the world’s ten tallest mountains, including Mount Everest, the highest point on Earth. Kathmandu is the nation’s capital and largest city.

Nepal is a place of festivals . Festivals may be linked with the remembrance of the departed soul, to herald the different seasons, to mark the beginning or end of the agricultural cycle, to mark the national events, or just family celebrations.  On a festive day the Nepalese take their ritual bath, worship different gods and goddesses, visit temple, observe fasting and undertake feasting.
    </string>
    <string name="bhutan_short_details">
        Bhutan, landlocked country of south . . .
    </string>
    <string name="bhutan_long_details">
        Bhutan, landlocked country of south-central Asia, located on the eastern ridges of the Himalayas. Historically a remote kingdom, Bhutan became less isolated in the second half of the 20th century, and consequently the pace of change began to accelerate. With improvements in transportation, by the early 21st century a trip from the Indian border to the Bhutanese capital, Thimphu, that once took six days by mule could be made in just a few hours by car along a winding mountain road from the border town of Phuntsholing. The governmental structure also changed radically. Reforms initiated by King Jigme Dorji Wangchuk (reigned 1952–72) in the 1950s and ’60s led to a shift away from absolute monarchy in the 1990s and toward the institution of multiparty parliamentary democracy in 2008.

Bhutan
Bhutan
The economic core of Bhutan lies in the fertile valleys of the Lesser Himalayas, which are separated from one another by a series of high and complex interconnecting ridges extending across the country from north to south. The political nucleus of Bhutan is centred in the Paro and Thimphu valleys in the Lesser Himalayan region. Its location between the Assam-Bengal Plain of India to the south and the Plateau of Tibet of southwestern China to the north gives the country considerable geopolitical significance.
    </string>
    <string name="srilanka_short_details">
        Sri Lanka, officially the Democratic  . . .
    </string>
    <string name="srilanka_long_details">
        Sri Lanka, officially the Democratic Socialist Republic of Sri Lanka (known as Ceylon before 1972) is an island nation in South Asia, located about 31 kilometres (19.3 mi) off the southern coast of India. Popularly referred to as the Pearl of the Indian Ocean, it is home to around twenty million people.

Due to its location in the path of major sea routes, Sri Lanka is a strategic naval link between West Asia and South East Asia, and has been a center of Buddhist religion and culture from ancient times.

Today, the country is a multi-religious and multi-ethnic nation, with nearly a third of the population following faiths other than Buddhism, notably Hinduism, Christianity and Islam. The Sinhalese community forms the majority of the population, with Tamils, who are concentrated in the north and east of the island, forming the largest ethnic minority. Other communities include the Muslim Moors and Malays and the Burghers.

Famous for the production and export of tea, coffee, rubber and coconuts, Sri Lanka boasts a progressive and modern industrial economy and the highest per capita income in South Asia. The natural beauty of Sri Lanka’s tropical forests, beaches and landscape, as well as its rich cultural heritage, make it a world famous tourist destination.

After over two thousand years of rule by local kingdoms, parts of Sri Lanka were colonized by Portugal and the Netherlands beginning in the 16th century, before the control of the entire country was ceded to the British Empire in 1815.

During World War II, Sri Lanka served as an important base for Allied forces in the fight against the Japanese Empire. A nationalist political movement arose in the country in the early 20th century with the aim of obtaining political independence, which was eventually granted by the British after peaceful negotiations in 1948.
    </string>
    <string name="mayanmar_short_details">
        Myanmar, country, located in the . . .
    </string>
    <string name="mayanmar_long_details">
      Myanmar, country, located in the western portion of mainland Southeast Asia. In 1989 the country’s official English name, which it had held since 1885, was changed from the Union of Burma to the Union of Myanmar; in the Burmese language the country has been known as Myanma (or, more precisely, Mranma Prañ) since the 13th century. The English name of the city that served as the country’s capital from 1948 to 2006, Rangoon, also was dropped in 1989 in favour of the common Burmese name, Yangon.

Myanmar
Myanmar
Sule pagoda
Sule pagoda
Sule pagoda, in the centre of Yangon, Myanmar.
In 2005 the government began to shift its administrative centre, first to the city of Pyinmana (some 200 miles [320 km] north of Yangon) and then to Nay Pyi Taw (Naypyidaw), a newly constructed city near Pyinmana. Nay Pyi Taw was proclaimed the capital of Myanmar in 2006.
    </string>
    <string name="south_korea_short_details">
The history of the Korean nation . . .
    </string>
    <string name="south_korea_long_details">
        The history of the Korean nation began in Manchuria and the Korean Peninsula when people started settling there 700,000 years ago. Representative historic sites associated with the Paleolithic Age, when people made tools of animal horns and chipped stone tools, include the Komun Moru ruins in Sangwon, Pyeongannam-do, the Jeongok-ri Site in Yeoncheon, Gyeonggi-do, the Seokjangri Prehistory Site in Gongju, Chungcheongnam-do, and the Durubong Cave Site in Cheongju, Chungcheongbuk-do. The early inhabitants of the peninsula survived by hunting animals and collecting edible plants in groups.

In Korea, the Neolithic Age began around 8,000 BCE. People started farming, cultivating cereals such as millet, and used polished stone tools. They started settling down permanently in places and formed clan societies. One of the most representative features of the Neolithic Age is comb-patterned pottery, examples of which have been found all across the Korean Peninsula, including in Amsadong, Seoul, in Namgyeong, Pyongyang, and in Suga-ri, Gimhae.
        The Bronze Age started around the 10th century BCE on the Korean Peninsula and the 15th century BCE in Manchuria. Historic sites associated with the Bronze Age are found in Liaoning and Jilin provinces, China and across the Korean Peninsula. With the development of the Bronze Age culture, a society emerged in which the head of a clan exercised great influence. The strongest clan leaders started merging many clans into one, and these groups very gradually developed into early states.

The tribes that played a central role in the establishment of Gojoseon, which emerged as the first recognizable state of the Korean people, believed in the King of Heaven and worshipped bears, respectively. The two factions jointly upheld Dangun Wanggeom as their chief priest and political leader. Gojoseon fostered an independent culture in Liaoning, China and along the Daedonggang River. By the 3rd century BCE, kings such as King Bu and King Jun had become powerful and bequeathed the throne to their sons. They established a solid system of rule, backed by high-ranking retainers and military officers.

Towards the end of the 3rd century, the Qin dynasty was replaced by the Han dynasty in China, creating a period of social upheaval. Many people moved southward to Gojoseon. Their leader, Wiman, acceded to the throne in 194 BCE and Gojoseon expanded its territory under his rule. By this time, Gojoseon had adopted Iron Age culture, developed agriculture and various handicrafts, and increased its military strength. It tried to monopolize profits, while serving as an intermediate in the trade between the Korean Peninsula and China, taking advantage of its geographical proximity to China. This led to confrontation between Gojoseon and the Han dynasty. Han attacked Gojoseon with a large number of ground and naval forces. Gojoseon defiantly resisted the attack and won a great victory in the early stage of the war, but its capital at Wanggeomseong Fortress fell after a year of war, and Gojoseon collapsed in 108 BCE.
    </string>
    <string name="china_short_details">
        Since China began to open up and . . .
    </string>
    <string name="china_long_details">
        Since China began to open up and reform its economy in 1978, GDP growth has averaged over 9 percent a year, and more than 800 million people have lifted themselves out of poverty. There have also been significant improvements in access to health, education, and other services over the same period.

China is now an upper-middle-income country. Although China has eradicated extreme poverty, a significant number of people remain vulnerable, with incomes below a threshold more typically used to define poverty in upper-mid­dle income countries.

China’s high growth based on investment, low-cost manufacturing and exports has largely reached its limits and has led to economic, social, and environmental imbalances. Reducing these imbalances requires shifts in the structure of the economy from manufacturing to high value services, from investment to consumption, and from high to low carbon intensity.

Over the past few years, growth has moderated in the face of structural constraints, including declining labor force growth, diminishing returns to investment, and slowing productivity growth. The challenge going forward is to find new drivers of growth while addressing the social and environmental legacies of China’s previous development path.

China’s rapid economic growth exceeded the pace of institutional development, and there are important institutional and reform gaps that China needs to address to ensure a high-quality and sustainable growth path. The role of the state needs to evolve and focus on providing a clear, fair and stable business environment, strengthening the regulatory system and the rule of law to further support the market system, as well as ensuring equitable access to public services to all citizens.

Given its size, China is central to many regional and global development issues. Although not the main source of historical cumulative emissions, China today accounts for 27 percent of annual global carbon dioxide and a third of the world’s greenhouse gas emissions – with per capita emissions now surpassing those of the European Union, although slightly below the OECD average and well below the level of the United States – and its air and water pollution affects other countries. Global environmental problems cannot be solved without China’s engagement. China’s growing economy is also an important source of global demand. Its economic rebalancing will create new opportunities for manufacturing exporters, though it may reduce demand for commodities over the medium-term.

China is a growing influence on other developing economies through trade, investment, and ideas. Many of the complex development challenges that China faces are relevant to other countries, including transitioning to a new growth model, rapid aging, building a cost-effective health system, and promoting a lower-carbon energy path.

Following China’s swift reopening after the COVID-19 outbreaks in late 2022, GDP growth is expected to rebound to 5.1 percent in 2023, from 3 percent in 2022. Growth will be led by a recovery in demand, particularly for services. Investment is expected to remain robust, supported by slower but sustained growth in infrastructure and manufacturing investment, as well as the gradual stabilization of property investment. Net exports are expected to weigh on growth, due to softer external demand coupled with a modest acceleration in import growth driven by the increase in domestic demand.

To support the ongoing recovery fiscal policy is expected to remain expansionary, albeit less so than in 2022. Monetary policy is likely to be relatively accommodative, and policy easing in the property sector will be maintained in 2023.

Over the medium term, China’s economy continues to confront a structural slowdown. Potential growth has been on a declining trend, reflecting adverse demographics, tepid productivity growth, and rising constraints to a debt-fueled, investment-driven growth model. Structural reforms are needed to reinvigorate the shift to more balanced high-quality growth.
    </string>
    <string name="australia_short_details">
        Australia covers an area of . . .
    </string>
    <string name="australia_long_details">
Australia covers an area of approximately 7.7 million square kilometres, making it the sixth largest country on earth and 22 times as big as Germany. The Commonwealth of Australia is the smallest continent on the planet and is located in the southern hemisphere. The continental landmass of Australia is divided into six states and three territories, along with seven other overseas territories (e.g. the Cocos Islands). The red continent can be split into three geographical regions: the Western Plateau, the Central Lowland and the Eastern Highlands. Australia is both the flattest and the driest inhabited continent, and has three different time zones. The capital of Australia is Canberra in the Australian Capital Territory. Canberra is Australia’s largest inland city and its eighth largest overall. Sydney, Melbourne, Brisbane and Perth are the best-known cities in Australia.
        Australia’s large desert areas are located in the Western Plateau, takes up around 60% of the country’s land mass. These areas include the Great Sandy Desert, the Great Victoria Desert and the Nullarbor Plain. In addition to these desert areas, the Western Plateau also contains small mountains and inselbergs. The Central Lowland (also known as the central basin) contains the Simpson Desert. This area is the driest region in the country but also contains Australia’s largest river system. In addition to the country’s lowest point, the area also contains salt lakes and freshwater lakes which dry up periodically.
The majority of Australia’s population lives in the east of the country, as most of the west and central areas are uninhabitable. This region also contains the Great Barrier Reef and the Great Dividing Range, the country’s most striking mountain area. The Great Dividing Range runs from north to south and is greater than 3200 km long. Tasmania is considered a continuation of the Great Dividing Range. The east of the country also contains the Snowy Mountains, Australia’s only Alpine region. Mount Kosciuszko is located here and is the highest mountain in Australia.
    </string>

</resources>